machree
fighting by your side ma'am you always
were a charmer
Divac just tell me one thing where'd you
learn to shoot like that 16-bit hero
you might be fast Genji but you ain't
faster than a bullet why don't we find
out
bad but I prefer a little bag to my
liquor
now predictable such an unsophisticated
taste
I heard there's a nice reward for
bringing you fellas in mm-hmm well
something out my
hey McCree do you know what time it is
well I'd say it's about now I see what
you're doing there
you know smoking is bad for your health
well I have faith you can get me patch
back up doc
mccrane where did you learn to shoot
like that was it jack
Gabriel always was a good shot but I got
a few pointers from the best that'd be
your mother
I taught you everything you know not
everything
teach you all my tricks lucky for me I
still have a few tricks of my own
you look ridiculous looked in the mirror
lately you were given those guns to toss
them around like trash I don't take
lessons from you
I heard there's a nice reward for
bringing you fellas in Troy
I bet you're a big fan of those
old-fashioned cowboy movies aren't you I
thought I was until I met you
pleasure working with you Macri if that
is your real name don't know what you
heard but my name's not Joe
let's remember that
someone had to do it seems fitting it'd
be me
you kill
I saw ghosts
like shooting a lady but for you I'll
make an exception
not fast enough
pretty handy with that bow